# TRISNA NADI SELAMET

Software Engineer [ Back End Development ]

Location: Bogor | No.Hp: +62812-9438-8977 | Email: nadi.selamet@gmail.com

## **SUMMARY**

I am a passionate person who enjoys creativity, and an IT programmer with knowledge of programming languages. I also have projects I have worked on myself in internal cases and also less than a year in manufacturing and corporate companies.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## PT. Sinar Mas Multiartha – Jakarta, Indonesia

Software Engineer [ Back End Development - Aug 2021 - Feb 2022]

- Development of back end systems business unit.
- Creation of data structures model database.
- Design function cleaning data and validation Rest API.
- Version control systems GIT or SVN knowledge and experience.
- Programming language java framework spring boot.

### PT. Suryaraya Rubberindo Industries – Bogor, Indonesia.

Intern website application [Sept 2019 - Nov 2019]

- Starting from analysis and data collection with observation, and brainstorming.
- One of the campus requirements. Using file Json and RDBMS Postgresql.
- Programming language Javascript.

### PT. Suryaraya Rubberindo Industries - Bogor, Indonesia

General Accounting [Mar 2015 - Dec 2020]

- Creation financial reports with vba macro.
- Creation Input accounting data into system with vba macro.
- · Search engine completeness of documents related to financial transaction with function excel.
- Process in the preparation of internal and eksternal

## **EDUCATION**

#### MERCU BUANA UNIVERSITY (2016 - 2020)

Bachelor's degree 2016 - 2020 Informatics IPK 3.37

## CERTIFICATION

- Certification Full-Stack Development.
- Certification Algorithm Basic.
- Certification Database Basic.

### TRAINING FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT

- Januari 2021 July 2021
- Javascript
- React Js
- Github
- posgreSQL

## LANGUAGE

Indonesia : Active English : Passive

## **SKILLS**

Node Js

MySQL

Microsoft Office

Javascript

PosgreSQL

LibreOffice

Java

Hbase (No-SQL)

Portfolio: https://trisna-nadi-selamet.github.io/Portfolio/